

■ tonyjly@gmail.com● tonyly.com• 425-343-3711

**♥** Kirkland, WA, 98033

#### INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- · Adapts to change quickly
- Excellent team communication
- Able to resolve team conflicts
- Maintains patients as top priority
- · Builds lasting patient trust and loyalty

### **SUMMARY**

Licensed pharmacist in Washington state. Possesses seven years of pharmacy experience in a community setting. Excellent interpersonal skills drives desire to build long-lasting relationships with patients, pharmacy colleagues, and fellow medical professionals. Seeking a pharmacist position that will provide the opportunity to practice high-quality, patient-centered health care.

## **EDUCATION**

# **UNIVERSITY OF NEW ENGLAND COLLEGE OF PHARMACY**

PharmD · 2016

### **UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON**

BS Microbiology · 2011

## **PROFESSIONAL LICENSURE**

**WASHINGTON PHARMACIST LICENSE** · PH60686691

Jul 2017 to Jun 2018 Sep 2014 to Present

**IMMUNIZATION CERTIFICATE** 

### **EMPLOYMENT**

CAREERSTAFF RX
Pharmacist Graduate Intern
Seattle, WA
Dec 2016 to Present

- Float to different pharmacy teams to provide relief in pharmacy technician roles
- Rapidly integrate into new pharmacy teams each shift and achieve cohesive teamwork
- Frequently learn unfamiliar pharmacy software systems
- · Advocate for patients to ensure they receive appropriate treatment while minimizing costs
- Answer clinical drug information questions from patients and pharmacy staff
- Assist in verifying accurate antibiotic dosing and dose intervals
- Provide patient education on proper medication usage and common side effects

## **TARGET PHARMACY**

**Pharmacist Intern; Pharmacy Assistant** 

Redmond, WA Aug 2007 to Aug 2014

- Answered clinical drug information questions from patients and pharmacy staff
- Assisted in verifying accurate antibiotic dosing and dose intervals
- Interpreted prescriptions via electronic patient profiles to minimize risk of DDIs and identify possible contraindications
- Interprofessional collaboration with prescribers via telephone to ensure accurate and appropriate therapy to patients
- Prepared oral antibiotic suspensions for patients
- Provided patient education on proper medication usage and possible side effects

#### UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON, DEPT OF PHARMACEUTICS

Research Technician II (Lin Lab)

Seattle, WA Jun 2010 to Aug 2012

- Primary research in identifying endogenous biomarkers for cytochrome P450 metabolism
- Extracted compounds of interest from human biological specimen via liquid-liquid extractions
- Conducted biological sample analysis via Mass Spectrometry (HPLC/MS-MS)
- · Compiled metabolomics database using Quadrupole-Time of Flight (Q-TOF) instrumentation

# **PROJECTS**

#### **VANCOMYCIN THERAPEUTIC DOSING AND MONITORING PROGRAM**

May 2015 to Aug 2015

Conducted retrospective outcomes evaluation on pharmacist-driven vancomycin dosing and monitoring protocols in inpatient and acute care settings. Spearheaded data analysis enhancement with pharmacy informatics integration to automate data collection.

# **LEADERSHIP**

Phi Lambda Sigma, Delta Chi Chapter · Historian 2014 to 2015

American College of Clinical Pharmacy (ACCP), Student Chapter · Historian 2014 to 2015

American Pharmacists Association, Academy of Student Pharmacists (APhA-ASP) · Communications VP 2013 to 2014